qikink.com 2018-06-02

# Privacy Policy - |

  1.  INTRODUCTION:

At QikInk.com, we respect the privacy of our visitors and customers (collectively referred to as “Users”).  QikInk.com does collect and use information provided by Users to better serve Users and to make QikInk.com as user friendly and accessible as possible.  This Privacy Policy spells out the information QikInk.com collects, how such information is collected, how the information is used and whether such information is disclosed to third parties.  QikInk.com reserves the right to make changes to any part of this Privacy Policy at its sole discretion, at any time and without prior notice.  Continued use of QikInk.com will constitute acceptance of any changes.  If this Privacy Policy is changed in any way, information concerning the changes will be available on this page.  QikInk.com strongly recommends that Users periodically review this Privacy Policy for any changes.

  2.  CONSENT TO USE INFORMATION:

By using the QikInk.com Website, each User consents to the collection and use of all information that the User provides to QikInk.com, all information that is provided to QikInk.com on behalf of that User, and all information that QikInk.com collects based on that User’s use of the site, including, without limitation, Personally Identifiable Information (defined below).  If User does not agree to this Privacy Policy, and the terms contained herein, User is not authorized to use the QikInk.com site.  The continued use of the QikInk.com site after any changes or amendments to this Privacy Policy shall signify the User’s acceptance of and consent to the changed or amended Privacy Policy.

  3.  QIKINK.COM’S PRIVACY PLEDGE:

QikInk.com is committed to protecting the privacy and personal information of Users at all times.  QikInk.com recognizes that this information belongs to the User, and will treat such information accordingly.  QikInk.com will not disclose any Personally Identifiable Information or confidential information of any User to any third parties, except as outlined in this Privacy Policy or as may be required by law.

  4.  QIKINK.COM USE OF PERSONAL AND NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION:

QikInk.com collects two kinds of information from on-line visitors, personal and non-personal information.  Visitors to the QikInk.com Website are not required to register, or provide any Personally Identifiable Information to access the QikInk.com site or review the products and services offered.  QikInk.com collects non-personal information to track the total number of guests visiting the QikInk.com site and to help QikInk.com improve the site and the services available on the site.  Such non-personal information includes the browser type and operating system being used by visitors, areas of the sites visited, date and time of access, host or service provider information and identification of the referring site.  This information is used exclusively for QikInk.com’s internal purposes and is not disclosed to any third parties.

Personally Identifiable Information, which means any information that can be used to identify or locate a specific person, including, but not limited to e-mail addresses, names, street addresses, phone numbers, fax numbers, credit card numbers and social security numbers, is collected only when voluntarily offered and solely for purposes clearly identified on the QikInk.com site.  Such Personally Identifiable Information is kept strictly confidential and will only be disclosed to third parties under the conditions described in Paragraph 5 of this Privacy Policy.

  5.   DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES:

QikInk.com may disclose Personally Identifiable Information as is required by law or under the following circumstances:

**Disclosure to Successor.**   QikInk.com may disclose User’s Personally Identifiable Information to any successor-in-interest of QikInk.com, such as a company that acquires QikInk.com and its assets.  Users will be notified by e-mail or notice on the QikInk.com Website of any change in ownership or control of Personally Identifiable Information.

**Disclosure to Third Party Service Providers and/or Online Partners**. QikInk.com may contract with various third parties to help provide, maintain and improve the QikInk.com Website and services.  For example, QikInk.com may use a third party contractor who processes payments, and may subcontract out production, fulfillment, analytics, reporting or other operations.  QikInk.com may also contract with third parties to help manage, monitor and optimize the QikInk.com Website and services and to assist in measuring the effectiveness of advertising, communications and use of the QikInk.com Website.  QikInk.com will use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent such third parties from disclosing Personally Identifiable Information, except for the purpose of providing the services in question.  However, QikInk.com can not guarantee that such third parties will not disclose User information.

Disclosure to Contest Partners.  QikInk.com may conduct contests for the benefit of, on behalf of, or in coordination with one or more third parties.  QikInk.com may share Personally Identifiable Information with said party or parties to the extent necessary to effectively run the Contest and award prizes.  Other than for the conducting of contests, QikInk.com does not share, rent or trade Personally Identifiable Information with third parties for cross-promotional purposes.

  6.  USE OF “COOKIES”:

QikInk.com may place an electronic “Cookie” in the browser files of a visitor’s computer.  Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual computer drive for record-keeping purposes.  Cookies themselves do not enable QikInk.com to access any personal information about visitors.  Cookies only allow QikInk.com to analyze a visitor’s use of the QikInk.com site.  This analysis helps QikInk.com better understand which areas of the QikInk.com site are more useful and popular so that improvements and updates can be made in the future.  QikInk.com does not use Cookies to retrieve information from a visitor’s computer that was not originally sent in a Cookie.

  7.  INFORMATION CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY:

QikInk.com is committed to preventing any unauthorized access to each User’s account.  QikInk.com has taken reasonable steps to maintain procedures and technology designed to prevent such unauthorized access.  However, the privacy and security of communication or data transmission over the internet cannot be guaranteed, because the internet is not a secure medium.  QikInk.com has taken reasonable steps to protect against unauthorized access to User’s accounts and Personally Identifiable Information used to administer User’s accounts. However, QikInk.com does not assume any responsibility for any harm, loss, or damage the User may experience or incur by the sending of personal and confidential information over the internet by or to QikInk.com.

  8.  USER ID’S AND PASSWORDS:

Each User is responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of his or her User ID and password, and is responsible for all activities that occur under his or her User account.  Each User agrees to immediately notify QikInk.com of any unauthorized use of his or her User ID, password or account, or any other breach of security known to the User.  QikInk.com will not be liable for any loss whatsoever arising from a User’s failure to comply with the security requirements and each User agrees to hold QikInk.com harmless from any and all losses that arise from any failure to comply.

  9.  NOTIFICATION OF SUSPECTED BREACH:

If any User suspects that any person has had unauthorized access to a User’s account, or access to a User’s information, including Personally Identifiable Information, such User should promptly send notification to QikInk.com at https://QikInk.com/contactus/ so QikInk.com can take any appropriate action to protect the User and his or her information, including Personally Identifiable Information.

  10. COMMUNICATIONS FROM QIKINK.COM:

QikInk.com may, from time to time, communicate with Users by e-mail to provide Users with information about QikInk.com services or special offers based on User’s preferences, interests, locations and/or past purchases. Users have the opportunity to opt out from such communications at any time. If Users receive such communications and wish to opt out, Users may do so by following the instructions included in each e-mail communication.

  11. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY POLICY:

The QikInk.com Website and services are intended for users ages 18 or older.  Users under the age of 18 are only permitted to use the QikInk.com Website under the direct supervision of their parent or legal guardian.  No one under the age of 13 is permitted to use the QikInk.com Website. QikInk.com does not knowingly collect or use Personally Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13.  QikInk.com will delete any information in the QikInk.com database which QikInk.com knows originated from a child under the age of 13.  QikInk.com will likewise delete any information in the QikInk.com database from a User between the ages of 13 and 17 at the request of the User or the User’s parent or legal guardian.

  12. INFORMATION THAT IS PUBLICLY AVAILABLE:

When you utilize certain services offered by QikInk.com, some information may be publicly available to other Users and visitors of the QikInk.com web site.  This information may include you User Name, the date you opened your QikInk.com account, the date you last log into your account, your age (if you choose to make it public) and your country of residence.  Although your QikInk.com User Name may be publicly available, your e-mail address is not publicly available.  Any information contained in any videos you record or submit to QikInk.com will also be publicly available
